Claire Phillips

Web Developer



(832) 741-8680



2597 Martina Drive, Apt. 6 Holt, MI, 48842

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Focused professional with 7 years of experience and a proven knowledge of database development, web programming, and web platform development. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

Communications Specialist

WILX, Lansing, MI / Nov 2017 - Present

- Developed and carried out social media communication strategies.
- Created appropriate content for events, programs, displays and communications.
- Wrote and published content across range of internal communication channels.

Digital Meteorologist

WNEM, Saginaw, MI / May 2015 - Oct 2017

- Maintained and edited digital assets including website, social media profiles and email marketing.
- Proposed and formulated social media strategy, campaigns and marketing ideas.
- Developed original content for day-to-day social media posts.
- Managed and grew all University social media accounts.
- Communicated and presented ideas in collaborative environment.

Part-time Meteorologist

WILX, Lansing, MI / Aug 2014 - Apr 2015

- Filled in on the weekends doing the weather on air
- Creating content for social media and the website
- Creating graphics for the newscasts

EDUCATION

Michigan State University East Lansing, MI

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp (Expected graduation Jul 2021)

Relevant Coursework

- Front end web development
- Back end web development

Baylor University Waco, TX

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Mass Communication and Journalism (May 2014)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Javascript	HTML	JQuery	Node.js
Web Development	Facebook Insight	Google Analytics	

CERTIFICATIONS

Full stack web Development boot camp Certificate

REFERENCES

References available upon request